[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Identify the 1996 movie from the quote: Listen up. They found Principal Himbry dead. He was gutted and hung from the goal post on the football field.", "correct_answer": "Scream", "incorrect_answers": ["Urban Legend", "Audition", "The Dark Half"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mount Rumpke is the highest point and the biggest landfill in Ohio. Its technical name is The Rumpke Sanitary Landfill.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the thriller this quote is taken from: Candy Cane....... Candy Cane.....", "correct_answer": "Joy Ride", "incorrect_answers": ["The Santa Clause", "The Candy Man", "The Others"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was James Coburn in the movie The Magnificent Seven?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Spectacled bear makes its habitat around the Andes tropical basin.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What must the Beast do in order to become human again in the 1991 animated movie Beauty and the Beast?", "correct_answer": "Find a woman who will love him back", "incorrect_answers": ["Sacrifice his life for a loved one", "Kill the woman he loves", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The title of the movie The Lost Boys was inspired by this childrens novel.", "correct_answer": "Peter Pan", "incorrect_answers": ["The Wizard of Oz", "Peter Rabbit", "The Secret Garden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous actor was Arthur Millers son-in-law?", "correct_answer": "Daniel  Day-Lewis", "incorrect_answers": ["Anthony Hopkins", "Kirk Douglas", "William Shatner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Steve McQueen was originally offered one of the starring roles in Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This German dish, whose name means sow\u2019s stomach is popular in Palatinate, a region in south-western Germany.", "correct_answer": "Saumagen", "incorrect_answers": ["Eisbein", "Bistec", "Haggis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is one of the most common health problems that comes from being overweight.", "correct_answer": "High blood pressure", "incorrect_answers": ["Fainting", "Vertigo", "Low blood pressure"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What British James Bond ally, portrayed by actor Charles Gray, confirms Bonds suspicions about the involvement of an unknown organization, in the 1967 movie, You Only Live Twice?", "correct_answer": "Henderson", "incorrect_answers": ["Blackwell", "Palmer", "Toombs"]}]